200 teeth. 0 chance.
Maneater is a mystery, thriller, horror film directed by Justin Lee.
A group of friends on vacation in a seeming island paradise are stalked by an
unrelenting great white after an accident leaves them stranded and left for dead.
Jessie Quilan, played by Nicky Whelan.
Harlan Burke, played by Trace Adkins.
Professor Sam Hoffman, played by Jeff Fahey.
Will Coulter, played by Shane West.
Sheriff Kua, played by Branscombe Richmond.
Sunny, played by Porscha Coleman.
Maneater is a 2022 American horror thriller film directed by Justin Lee, starring Nicky
Whelan, Shane West, Trace Adkins, Branscombe Richmond and Jeff Fahey.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.